♪Just wanna say hello♪
♪ فقط أريد أن أقول مرحبًا ♪
♪Hello♪
♪ مرحبا ♪
♪You are so unstoppable♪
♪ أنت لا يمكن إيقافك ♪
=Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2= =Episode 8=
= Here Is My Exclusive Indulge S2 = = الحلقة 8 =
I have a picture of the real daughter of the Yun Group.
لدي صورة الابنة الحقيقية لمجموعة يون.
Dad.
أب.
Have a look.
الق نظرة.
This is the real daughter of the Yun Group.
هذه هي الابنة الحقيقية لمجموعة يون.
Look at that ugly nose.
انظر إلى ذلك الأنف القبيح.
Now look at hers.
الآن انظر إلى راتبها.
And those small eyes.
وتلك العيون الصغيرة.
Look at her eyes.
انظر الى عينيها.
And the mouth and eyebrows.
والفم والحاجبين.
She's nothing like it in the picture.
إنها لا تشبهها في الصورة.
Rongrong.
رونغ رونغ.
You were even uglier when you were little.
كنت حتى أقبح عندما كنت صغيرا.
Girls become prettier as they get older.
تصبح الفتيات أجمل مع تقدمهن في السن.
Auntie, do you think
عمتي ، هل تعتقد
I was too ugly as a kid?
كنت قبيحة جدا عندما كنت طفلا؟
Your auntie didn't mean that.
عمتك لم تكن تعني ذلك.
If auntie wants my picture,
إذا أرادت العمة صورتي ،
you can just tell me.
يمكنك فقط إخباري.
There's no need to look for it in secret.
ليست هناك حاجة للبحث عنها سرا.
You should apologize to Xiangxiang.
يجب أن تعتذر لـ Xiangxiang.
But...
ولكن...
It's okay, grandpa.
لا بأس يا جدي.
Auntie's intention was good.
كانت نية العمة جيدة.
Since Xiangxiang said so,
بما أن شيانغشيانغ قال ذلك ،
we'll let it go.
سنتركها تذهب.
It's my fault this time.
إنه خطأي هذه المرة.
As an apology to Xiangxiang,
كاعتذار لـ Xiangxiang ،
I'll throw a socialite's party tomorrow.
سأقيم حفلة اجتماعية غدا.
You have to come, Xiangxiang.
عليك أن تأتي ، Xiangxiang.
I think...
أظن...
Maybe next time.
ربما في المرة القادمة.
Sihan.
سيهان.
There'll only be girls on the party.
لن يكون هناك سوى فتيات في الحفلة.
No man will be chasing her around.
لن يطاردها أي رجل.
Just let her come. Don't worry.
فقط دعها تأتي.  لا تقلق.
But I...
لكن أنا...
I just got back from abroad.
لقد عدت للتو من الخارج.
I'm so tired.
أنا متعب جدا.
The jet lag is such a pain.
إرهاق السفر مثل هذا الألم.
Oh my.
يا بلادي.
So you are still blaming me?
إذن أنت لا تزال تلومني؟
Xiangxiang.
شيانغشيانغ.
Your auntie is doing this for you.
عمتك تفعل هذا من أجلك.
Just go.
فقط اذهب.
You can take this opportunity
يمكنك اغتنام هذه الفرصة
to get to know the friends of our family.
للتعرف على أصدقاء عائلتنا.
Grandpa...
الجد ...
Yeah. I believe
نعم.  أعتقد
that auntie will treat you well there.
تلك العمة سوف تعاملك بشكل جيد هناك.
Of course,
بالطبع،
I will treat her well.
سوف أعاملها بشكل جيد.
That was a long day.
كان ذلك يوما طويلا.
Thankfully, nothing went wrong.
لحسن الحظ ، لم يحدث خطأ.
What about the party tomorrow?
ماذا عن الحفلة غدا؟
Can Miss Yun manage it on her own?
هل يمكن للآنسة يون إدارتها بمفردها؟
Go home first.
اذهب للمنزل أولا.
I'm off work. Drop me off at home.
أنا خارج العمل.  أوصلني في المنزل.
Which home?
أي بيت هو؟
Our home.
بيتنا.
Your home?
منزلك؟
What?
ماذا؟
I mean drop me off at my place.
أعني أوصلني إلى مكاني.
No way.
مستحيل.
You have to live with me from now on.
عليك أن تعيش معي من الآن فصاعدا.
Fu Rong is suspicious of your identity. She would have eyes on you.
يشك فو رونغ في هويتك.  سيكون لديها عيون عليك.
It's too risky if you still live at your place.
إنها مخاطرة كبيرة إذا كنت لا تزال تعيش في مكانك.
And...
و...
You...
أنت...
You agreed?
وافقتم؟
Of course. No more rent or bills!
بالطبع.  لا مزيد من الإيجار أو الفواتير!
You are a really good boss.
أنت حقا رئيس جيد.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Hello, Miss Yun.
مرحبا يا آنسة يون.
I'm Butler Chen.
أنا بتلر تشين.
If you have any needs,
إذا كان لديك أي احتياجات ،
just tell me.
فقط أخبرني.
Okay. Thank you.
تمام.  شكرًا لك.
Your butler looks like a good person.
الخادم الخاص بك يبدو وكأنه شخص جيد.
Fu Rong pretends to be looking after me.
يتظاهر فو رونغ بأنه يعتني بي.
She placed those people around me.
لقد وضعت هؤلاء الناس حولي.
Especially that butler.
خصوصا ذلك الخادم الشخصي.
Be careful around him.
كوني حذرة من حوله.
Problems of the rich people.
مشاكل الأغنياء.
Anyway, in this house,
على أي حال ، في هذا المنزل ،
you can't trust anyone
لا يمكنك الوثوق بأحد
except Chu He.
باستثناء Chu He.
You guys really don't have other worries, huh?
أنتم حقا يا رفاق ليس لديكم مخاوف أخرى ، أليس كذلك؟
Living your life like you are in a movie.
تعيش حياتك كما لو كنت في فيلم.
Oh.
أوه.
Why doesn't your auntie like you?
لماذا لا تحبك عمتك؟
You don't need to know.
لا تحتاج إلى معرفة.
Fu Rong.
فو رونغ.
She's not my blood relative.
إنها ليست قريبة دمي.
My grandpa adopted her.
تبناها جدي.
So you only have one family in this world,
لذلك ليس لديك سوى عائلة واحدة في هذا العالم ،
just like me.
فقط مثلي.
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
What's for dinner?
ماذا يوجد للعشاء؟
There must be much delicious food.
يجب أن يكون هناك الكثير من الطعام اللذيذ.
You can go now.
يمكنك الذهاب الآن.
Enjoy your dinner.
استمتع بعشائك.
Abalone? Lobster?
أذن البحر؟  سرطان البحر؟
Or Kobe steak?
أو شريحة لحم كوبي؟
This is all?
هذا كل شيء؟